Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
This is Ebisu Shimizu, middle school.
And so it begins.
Today, Ayaka Yasumoto will be conducting this session.
And who are you guys?
Attendance number 10, Aya Kuchigami.
Please.
And who are you?
I am number 12, Rika Nakayama.
I'll start the title call.
Ebisu's
The Delightful and Funny Showroom of Ebisu
Here we go. Today is the 41st Ebisu's Spectacular and Unwelcoming Showroom.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
How long have you two been together?
Yuko recently?
I haven't seen you since last month.
Last month?
We've been here quite a bit.
According to the script, it's been August for me.
Wow!
That's a long time.
That's a lot.
I haven't been since September.
So you two have been together for a while.
It's been quite a while.
It's been a long time, everyone in the showroom.
It's been a while.
Yes, that's right.
Ebichu's Spectral and Wandering Showroom is our little sister show.
This is the sister show of Ukka's showroom.
This will be the first distribution after the start of the year 2022.
We look forward to seeing you all this year.
We are looking forward to seeing you all again this year.
It's going to be a very exciting year.
Let's start ranking, Mr. Nakayama.
Yes, let's start with the ranking.
Let's start the ranking.
Ranking.
Fifth place.
Mother.
Yay.
4th place.
Ah, there it is.
There you are.
Thank you very much.
Third place.
Mr. Yachin.
Thank you very much.
And second place.
Midoru Sakurai.
Midoru-san.
Mirepen.
At markre.
Le? Le? Le? It says "le"?
It says "Le".
Thank you very much.
Leon.
Leonan.
Maybe it's a long name.
But it only says "Le".
Thank you very much.
And the first place.
Thank you, Mr. Mayugi.
Thank you very much.
All the original avatars of Ebichu are now ready.
You already have comments?
That's great.
This avatar is really powerful, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Comment.
I read everyone's crackling comments.
Ai-chan said Russia is cute too.
Thank you.
It's warm.
It's warm even though it's indoors.
If you register in the showroom, you can use this avatar for free or for a fee.
You can use this avatar for free or for a fee.
I hope you all get one and use it.
If you click on the twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen
You can advertise this distribution by clicking on the Twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen.
If you could all help us out and tweet about it, please do so.
I can't believe how cute the three of you are today.
I said they are cute.
They're so cute!
Do you have any suggestions for words to add?
Do you have an avatar with the hashtag?
Isn't that a new trend these days?
Ebitu-san is always using hashtags.
Ai-chan talked in a gyaru voice.
I've been doing that ever since.After I'm done.
What are you going to do today?
I'll post a picture of the three of us when I'm done.
I'll hashtag it.
Okay, I'll do that.
Do you have anything in common with the three of us?
In the comments.
You can ask for it.
We're looking for commonalities.
Please decide on a hashtag for the three of us today.
We used to have one hashtag after all.
We've been doing it for a long time.
Gal, you said, "This is how flowers wither and the soil withers.
That's right.
And that was it? Like a fossil in my mind.
It became a fossil.
I think I became a fossil in the end.
I wonder what we have in common.
What do we have in common?
There are fossils in the soil.
The three of us.
Common point of contact.
Riko Nakayama and her merry band of friends are our friends, aren't they?
That's good. Let's use it.
Hashtag.
Should we use "Delightful Friends"?
Let's do that.
We'll all wear it.
Are you sure?
Hashtag.
Riko Nakayama and her merry band.
Are you sure?
I wonder how many people are out there.
Oh, but look.
Asa-san and everyone else are also fun-loving friends.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's good, isn't it?
By all means, please tweet with the hashtag Nakayamashiko and her merry band of friends.
Yes, please.
Reclactors, please.
Then, it's time to spread the word here.
A photo of the three of us.
A picture like "Ms. Nakayama with her delightful friends.
Oh, okay.
Manager.
Where?
There you are.
It's funny.
Delightful.
Okay, let's hashtag this without the hashtag Nakayamashiko and Yukari Arakamashi.
Yes. Please do it.
If you all retweet it, please give me a lot.
Please do.
Oh, wait.
What do we have in common?
Shamidare said,
Common ground, they're from the same brotherhood.
Oh, yeah, us.
Mochi.
We're representatives.
Yes, yes, representative.
They say they represent their siblings.
You say that?
That's exactly what you said. Stupidity is rare.
It was rare.
You might be a moron if you're careful.
Yes, you could be.
So, you see, Ebituaries, lately.
Recently,
It was just the end of the year, so there were a lot of things that happened a month ago.
Yes, I know. There was the reboot of the big arts and crafts festival.
Yes, that's right. We had various singing contests and so on.
The famous members were in the New Year's Eve show, weren't they?
That's right.
Yes.
We did,
There's a lot of talk about looking back on the big show,
It really feels like that time has come too soon,
It feels like a long time ago.
Really?
I understand.
It's strange, isn't it?
It's so much fun,
It feels like a distant memory,
It's been, like, a month.
That's right.
It's been a long time,
You've been here since 27, right?
That's right.
So, just about a month.
About a month.
Not even a month.
That's fast. It's the end of a month in 2022.
What?
It just started.
It just started and it's already over.
January goes by so fast, doesn't it? Really.
So, I'm already in a New Year's slump,
That's right.That's right.
All year round, you know, blah, blah, blah,
It started more than usual.
That's right.
He's glad he won.
Are you a college student?
Yeah, I am.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
There are a lot of artists here, aren't there?
Yeah.
How about those who came?
We received a lot of feedback from the university students, who also commented on the show.
Yes, I went both days.
Thank you very much.
Everyday Mach.
New NES writer.
Ahhh...
I know what the three singers are.
I know what they are.
Now that you know who the three singers are, you're looking forward to the CS broadcast.
That's great.
We haven't seen them on film either.
We can enjoy it on film, too. This time.
It's February.
It's almost here.
I would like to ask everyone to come out in February to look back on their memories.
And I think the "Memory Song Contest" was also quite intense.
It was intense.
We also performed an idol medley.
And ani-songs.
We also performed ani-songs.
And then there was Enieni.
That's right.
Hiroshita. It was the first time I performed there after the big show.
It was pretty intense.
Yes, it was. It was intense. The end of the year was really intense.
It was packed, wasn't it?
From the big school arts and crafts festival. And you also did some recording.
That's right.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
I learned a lot.
It was amazing.
That's for sure.
Gourrier was so sharp and sharp.
That's right.
Gorlier was the hardest. Honestly.
Really.
Gorrie, you know, cheerleading choreography, it's hard to get used to it,
At first, I was able to take a video of the choreography three days before the big show.
Oh, yeah. Let's finish it.
What? We have a big concert coming up, and you're choreographing.
I'm not going to do it. Like that.
What should we do?
I was in a hurry, wasn't I? I was in a huge hurry.
Yes, Hinata-chan played a song by AKB of Nihon Hammony in the idol medley.
So after the rehearsal and the show, we were all playing "Cocona" backstage,
It was amazing.
That's exactly what we did, with everyone from Mr. Hyuga's Kimishimihatante,
Oh, we did it.
It was like, "We did it!
We did it.
It was amazing. But now that I think about it, it was a lot of fun.
It was fulfilling.
And the New Year's Eve program seemed to be going smoothly,
We were having fun, delivering the program and saying things,
And then we went on winter break.
Yes, winter break.
So, you know.
Oh, yeah.
What did you do? At the beginning of the year.
At the beginning of the year, I stayed in and took it easy at the beginning of the year.
That's nice.
You know, the one where you sneezed on me?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
With Ma-chan.
How many more people did you have in the end?
How many more?
There are no more, but there are four now.
Four?
Dog, dog, cat, cat.
But, you know, it's been a long time since I've been surrounded by pets.
You are usually alone, right?
That's right, I'm all alone.
Do you remember Hinata-chan, too, Ma-chan?
I don't remember him.
But it would be sad if you forget me.
Sad?
Am I sad? That's why, originally,
I guess I'm pretty sure,
I'm back! I'm not the type of person who says, "I'm back!
You're back. I was like, "Oh, you're back.
Oh, it's you! I'm back.
That's how I feel.
You know, I've heard stories from all kinds of people,
They came to pick me up at the door,
They waited for me for a long time,He waited for me for a long time,
And the moment I opened the door, I was like, "Wow! I was like, "Wow!
I opened the door and finally,
And then I saw him,
Oh, it's you! Come on! I was like, "Come on!
Come on, come on.
That's right. Come here.
That's cute.
Hee~.
Is he older than Hinata?
In terms of human age, she's not much older than me,
But then, she's like a daughter to you.
I see. From the moment she arrived,
I think she's always looked down on me,
We're already above you! Like we're above you.
Oh, that's what it looks like,
So I said, "Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, I see.
I see.
It would be nice to live like that, hunting pets.
It's nice, isn't it?
It's cute, isn't it?
If you had a dog or a cat, which would you keep?
Which one would you keep? Do you want to have a cat or a dog?
I don't know,
I want to walk with them,
I want to walk with him,
I think I'd like a dog.
It is true that walking is something you long for, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I think I'd like to be a dog, too.
I guess so. Cats have a strong image of being stuffy, don't they?
It makes me a little sad.
If you were to do it, I'd feel like I couldn't sleep.
I'd feel like I couldn't sleep.
It would be nice to have a dog that comes to you and says, "Wan wan wan.
It's cute, isn't it?
Recently, there are many people who have animals, not just dogs or cats, but other animals that they can keep.
You can keep a miniature pig. Yes, yes, yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Cute. Yes, yes, yes.
They're called kings. There are many kings.
During Golden Week, you know, ours, ours. Ours.
Do any of you have otters or something? I mean...
Hmm.
Oh, yes, we do.
Oh, Kayla?
What?
A lizard?
Oh, you have a lizard?
Date-Kayla from the Tohoku region.
Oh, wow.
They say celebrities are raw-livered cormorants.
Celebrities are raw-livered cormorants.
Raw liver.
Coca? Raw liver.
Did you eat rice cakes? Because I ate a rice cake.
I ate rice cake.
I did.
Did you?
What kind of rice cake do you like?
Sugar and soy sauce.
Wrapped in seaweed.
Wow! Delicious!
After all, that's not the point.
There are so many different kinds.
There are all kinds of things, and they're all delicious.
But I just end up going there.
Oh, that's nice.
I haven't eaten rice cakes.
I wanted to do that, too.
I really wanted to try it.
So, I had three rice cakes mysteriously.
Mysteriously?
I mysteriously had three of them at home,
I don't like to have all the seasonings.
This is coming from someone who doesn't cook at all.
You don't want to have seasonings?
You don't know where to put all the seasonings.
Soy sauce, ponzu vinegar, and so on.
Or adding more and more sugar,
I have an image that the kitchen will become a mess.
If you put a bottle of ponzu or something that looks like ponzu in the kitchen, you don't know where to put it.
I don't like the idea of having a bottle that looks like Ponzu, or Ponzu sauce, just sitting in the kitchen.
I don't know, the color is messy.
I don't know.
Which is better?
The taste,
You don't end up eating it?
I have soy sauce at home, but no sugar,
That's why I stopped.
I didn't want to buy sugar.
He told me I should replace it with a container of the same design.
So I moved it.
So it wouldn't look lived-in.
That's right.
There are simple ones sold at 100-yen and Muji.
So I'll just go with that.
I think I'll finally have it all.
There are soy sauce and balsamicos.
Why those two?Why those two?
What?
Balsamicos and olive oil.
But I keep vinegar and soy sauce in the fridge.
You don't mind if I put them in the fridge?
I put a lot of things in the fridge.
Balsamicos,
Balsamicos are in the fridge too?
I don't know.
Why do people keep balsamicos in the fridge?
Why don't we just put them in a storage cabinet or something?
They're not going home.
What's in the fridge?
Salsisses is not necessary.
Sugar, soy sauce, vinegar.
Sugar, salt, vinegar.
Says soy sauce, right?
Says soy sauce.
Sauce.
Do you have all of them?
No, sir.
Not sauces.
What's sauce?
I thought it was sauce.
It's miso!
Miso!
Isn't sauce that important?
We all know what it is.
Sauce.
Miso!
Oh no!
Sugar, salt, vinegar, soy sauce, miso.
Do you have any?
I don't have all of them.
Sugar, salt,
Salt, soy sauce, vinegar.
No vinegar.
Do you have salt, soy sauce, miso?
I only have soy sauce and miso.
Well, can we bring our own?
If we bring our own.
We'd also need sugar.
If we all bring our own, we'll have the seasoning.
We've got the sarcissus.
You're saying we should have it all?
That's right.
Now we know the three of us don't really cook.
We can get by with soy sauce.
That's true.
Everything tastes better with soy sauce.
Yes, yes, yes.
What do you put on food if you think it's not seasoned enough?
Salt?
Soy sauce.
My favorite seasoning.
Favorite seasoning?
White or yakiniku sauce.
I know! It's delicious!
In one piece.
Isn't this good?
The first thing I bought was yakiniku sauce.
I bought yakiniku sauce too.
I know!
You can handle it.
You can use any kind of yakiniku sauce.
It's a man's idea.
It says "bachelor college.
But everyone says that yakiniku sauce is the best.
That's right.
Mentsuyu is delicious.
I understand. I do.
It's good.
I understand. Mayonnaise, too.
If you leave mayonnaise on the table, you put mayonnaise on everything.
That's right.
It says "The three idiots" on the label.
No, no, no.
You're not stupid, are you?
It's delicious even with a simple seasoning.
Yes, yes.
Sesame oil.
Sesame oil is good.
There was a time when all I had in my house was sesame oil, furikake (sprinkled on rice), and rice that I could cook.
That was all I had for about a month.
So I ate rice with furikake and sesame oil every day.
It's delicious.
It's delicious. I promise.
I recommend it to everyone.
Try it. With rice.
Furikake and nori balls on rice?
Furikake on rice and a dab of sesame oil.
Nori dama is delicious.
Try it, it's delicious.
Yasumoto family's B-class gourmet.
Let's try it.
What were you talking about?
I don't know.
What should we eat for New Year's Eve and New Year's Day?What to eat rice cake at New Year's Eve and New Year's Day.
Sugar and soy sauce.
We don't have sugar.
I'm an idol of condiments.
I was the seasoning idol.
If the three of us share our concerns, we'll be fine.
Do you have a rice cooker?
No. But you can cook rice in the microwave.
But you can cook rice in the microwave.
I learned that the other day.
Mirei's cooking TV show.
I was on it the other day.
I cooked rice in the microwave for 7 minutes.
Rice.
Uh, you know...
Rice. I made risotto.
You take raw rice, add water, milk, and other stuff, and cook it for 7 minutes.
Can you do it?
Yes, it's possible.
You just need a little bit of thinner and you can cook it like this.
After that, you cook the risotto in various ways, and the outside gets cooked.
So, yes.
I think it can be cooked in about 3 minutes.
I heard that it really only takes 7 minutes.
That's right.
If you think about it that way, you don't need a rice cooker for now.
It's just for one person.
I have a small rice cooker. It's a Muji.
You have a small rice cooker?
But I've never cooked rice. I wanted to eat sweet potatoes.
Potatoes?
That's exactly what you'd get if you cook them.
But it's not. Rice cooker tastes better.
I did it at my parents' house, and it tasted better in the rice cooker.
So, do it for real.
We'll lend you our rice cooker.
We'll share.
I'll lend you our rice cooker.
Really.
It's more like the sweetness of a sweet potato.
Baked sweet potatoes are a mysterious thing.
It also makes the sweet potato sticky. Rice cooker.
But it takes time.
Just like cooking rice.
All you have to do is press the "cook" button.
What do you mean, "lend me the rice cooker"? He said, "Call me at home.
Sure.
Have them come to your house.
That's funny.
Do you like your rice hard? Or soft?
I can't see his face.
I can't see your face.
It's the KLK5 World Land 2022 test.
I like sticky ingredients.
Sticky? Porridge?
You mean porridge?
I don't have any textbooks.
I don't hear about it. Not much.
I really like it loose.
I often tell my mom that I like it loose when I cook rice, and I ask her to do it.
Most of my family members don't do it.
They don't do it.
So when Aya-chan tells me to do it, it's like...
I'm like, "Dad or brother, get out of here.
And again, it's loose.
Harder?
If I had to say, I'd say hard is better.
Lunch boxes are often hard, right?
Because they get cold.
Because they get watery, they are often hard.
Then they are dry and crumbly.
So I put them in really hot,
I like the rice in bento boxes that are really hot, but after a while the water comes out and the rice becomes soggy.
I've been told I'm a grandmother.
Teeth problems.
It's hard to eat.
But then again, isn't microwavable rice pretty soft?
Soft and tender.
I prefer it that way.
It's overwhelmingly hard. I like it hard.
But I'm trying to lighten it up a bit. Really?
I can relate. There you are. That's good.
I've never seen it before. I'm sure.
I wonder what it is. What is it that he is so particular about?
That gooey, gooey, seaweed ball and sesame oil? Yes, yes, yes.
It's a gooey mess.
Not tasty? It's not tasty, but it's tasty.
Or maybe it's the stickiness of the rice that comes out.
Oh, I like it.
But I always say it's soggy.
Really?
We're the same.
Oh, you can't drink ramen?
Ramen is hard ramen.
Oh, they're hard there.
Why?
Balikata Ramen.
Barikata Ramen.
Yes, when I was in Fukuoka on an expedition...
They called it "balikata ramen".He called it balikata ramen.
Heh.
Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Ramen?
You don't like it too soft?
Normal hardness?
A little bit hard.
Hard?
I think most people like their ramen pretty hard, don't you?
That's right.
Tonkotsu (pork bone) ramen is usually like that.
If it's too soft, the soup is too strong.
Too much flavor.
If it's too hard, you can eat it quickly.
What about udon?
Udon?
Udon noodles should be soft.
Are udon noodles hard or soft?
Yes, there is! Yes, quite a lot.
Udon noodles are supposed to be eaten with a side dish.
So soft that you can chew it with your tongue when you eat it.
Then, the softer ones.
Wow!
Hakata's udon has a very soft color.
Really?
Expensive udon.
But the sticky ones are good too.
That's rice, like glutinous rice.
How are udon noodles made?
What do you make udon noodles with?
Potato starch.
No, no, no...
Sorry, sorry.
They never harden.
I've never heard of it.
You know what I'm talking about?
Oh, my God, you're sure?
Flour and water.
They'll know how to live with it.
Flour.
Idiot.
They'll know we're not from the same family.
They'll know.
They'll know!
Don't do that!
Let's go next time.
Let's go next.
Next?
Yes, ma'am.
I didn't know what was better.
I'd like to move on to the next section.
"Hilarious and Fabulous Strangers Kake Sobe".
I heard that this is a project we did at a showroom in the Uka showroom.
I'd like to present my resolutions for this year in a kakezoe.
But here's what's different
The difference from a normal kessobe is
I don't want you to write your own aspirations.
I want to write about other people's aspirations
I would like to imagine myself as someone else
I would like to imagine and present my own aspirations.
Then, the members who are not here today
I'm going to think about my aspirations while pretending to be someone else.
See you later.
I thought today's show was great.
May I write it vertically?
Yes, I liked the kakegane.
I'll have to do an impersonation.
I'll let you guys guess whose resolutions I'm writing.
I don't know.
It's difficult, isn't it?
I heard it's a long introduction.
You're right. We have to wait until we get to the project.
That's for sure.
Okay.
It raises the bar.
I was mute when I did this.
It's hard.
It's hard, isn't it?
Imagine.
Imitation.
You know who's good at this?
Who's there? The shrimp.
Kaho.
Kaho, you just do your best impersonations.
You're the best at impersonating the manager.
He's the best.
I'm really good at it.
You're right.
You're good.
I hear you can draw something funny too.
That's true.
People don't know who or what we draw.
So do we.
Oh, I could do it.
I did it. That was fast.
Who's going to make the announcement?
Okay, Hinata, write.
I finished quickly.Because I finished writing early.
From the sun.
Can I just say the usual?
Please announce your aspirations.
My goal for this year is,
I'm going to do my best.
What? Do your best?
What do you mean by "do my best"?
Last year,
I haven't been in it until now.
I worked hard last year, too,
I worked hard last year, and I'm going to work hard this year, too,
I'm going to work hard this year, too,
I'm going to work hard this year, too.
Really?
You sure you can do it? I'll do it!
You know what I'm saying? It's a little bit like that? I don't know if I can tell. Can you tell, fans?
I'll probably do it.
Maybe is not good enough.
If you decide to do it, you will do it, right?
I will do it.
I'm not going to say it clearly until the end.
I'll say it. I'll do my best.
You'll do your best?
Tapipun
Tapipun.
Then who is your name?
Cocoyona.
What? What is it?
What? What did she say?
Cocoyona.
Oh, Cocoyona.
Yes, that's right. That was Cocoyona's ambition.
That's why you look like her.
Yes, we do.
Yuko, you know, you named yourself so fast.
She said, "Cocoyona.
That's true.
You're quick with the heart part.
Cocoyona.
She's got your features.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, good.
You're right, they do look alike.
That's good.
He's got my features.
You know, usually when people ask me what my goals are.
I'll probably say something like, "I'm doing well this year.
"I'm going to do my best.
I think he probably said something like that.
I don't think they'll ever say what they're going to do.
I don't think I'll ever say anything specific.
Roughly.
Isn't that just one kanji character?
It's not a single kanji character.
But why?
I'm curious about you, Yoriko.
I might have made a mistake.
It's a single kanji character.
Next, let's hear your excitement!
My sister told me to speak loud and clear, so I will speak loud and clear.
This year's Kanji character is "go forward.
This will be my first anniversary as a member, so even though I am younger than my sister, I have to pull myself together,
I will do my best to pull my sister and myself along.
My sister told me to speak clearly, so I will speak clearly.
You are really serious.
You are so serious.
Today, too, I was practicing for the FC event, and I came home alone.
She said she studied yesterday, too.
What? You didn't study?
I studied.
I'm lying.
I'm Noka KAZANO.
I'm Kazan no Noka.
You knew we were leaving.
Attendance number 15, this is Kazano no Noka.
I'm Kazaminonoka.
My sister told me to speak clearly.
That's all I'm going to say.
That's all I have to say.
That's good.
Now, the rest of the story.
One kanji character.
That's a little too much for my taste, isn't it?
Next.
Who is next?
May I make a presentation?
Yes.
Who?
Okay, my
This year's
I'll introduce my speech of the year.
Who told this to Richu?
Let's say it in a nice way.
Let's say it.
It's cheap, isn't it?
I want to eat something delicious.
I want to do something fun.I want to do something fun.
Which is it?
I want to go snowboarding or something.
Which one?
If it's snowboarding, I want to go snowboarding.
I want to go snowboarding.
What do you want to eat?
Something good?
I'm going to a convenience store. What do you want to eat?
Something tasty!
That's hard!
What do you want to buy?
Something tasty!
I know who you are.
But I'm pretty sure the viewer has two choices.
Two choices.
Let's take it a little further, shall we?
Yeah, a little bit.
I wonder.
Ask some questions.
Talk like a girl.
Well, let me ask you something.
Do you have a question for me?
What's your favorite food?
Good food.
I guess so. Sure, sure.
What are some popular poses these days?
Poses that are popular these days.
But isn't this the latest trend?
Do you have any particular insta-focus?
I use a pink filter all over.
You get the idea, right?
You get it now, don't you?
You can tell by this.
I try to keep it consistent.
Any recent purchases?
I bought a sparkly bag.
I'm going to get in trouble.
Long legs, right?
Super long.
Very long.
My waist is like this.
Legs are long?
Super long.
When she and Aya are side by side, it's a big win.
Big winner.
What's your name?
Who is it?
Mirei Hoshina.
Congratulations.
But I still have to choose between Cocona and Mine.
I guess so.
It's hard to decide.
But I heard that Mine often does the side pose.
That's true.
You do it.
At the photo session the other day, you did this amazing one.
What is this?
A heart?
He's making a heart with his cheek.
Heart?
With his hands and cheeks.
Because it's a heart. Let's try one more time.
Like this?
You were born in the age of social networking, right?
That's right.
I was born in it.
You're a gal from the Heisei era? I guess so.
That's right.
Because everyone gets mad at me.
They get double-stage anger.
No, no, no.
Cocona and I were arguing about gal, weren't we?
We're doing it. You've been doing it recently.
We've been doing it lately.
That's what we're doing.
It's like the Heisei era.
It's interesting.
That's what I thought.
Can you vote for me?
After all.
Yes.
Number 1.
Okay, then, please vote in the comments to see who looks the most like you.
Number.
Please comment with this number.
Voting function.
It's a great idea, you say.
Really?
Try using the voting function.
If it's a corner, I wonder what's the difference between it and Mirei.
I wonder how they would differ.
First of all, maybe they use honorifics, right?
That's for sure.
But if you say you can speak to me in a casual way, I'll become an adult, won't I?
That's right.Right.
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
Coconner said he'll talk about persimmons soon. That's true. He likes persimmons.
So, here are the results of the voting!
Number one is number one.
Yay!
At 43.5,
Nunopi.
And in second place,
Huh? Me? Could it be?
It's true.
Number three.
31%.
Me.
Yay. Yay!
You made a mistake.
And?
And second and third place,
Me.
Mr. Nakayama.
But it was a very subtle third place, even though none of us looked like him.
I mean, it wasn't overwhelming,
It wasn't overwhelming.
That's for sure.
I felt that the entries were well distributed.
It's difficult. Next time, I'll do more impersonations.
It's not easy to imitate the members.
It's not easy. Like what they say,
I can understand what they are going to say, but I don't know if the fans can understand it.
But I'm not sure if the fans can understand it or not.
Did you say they all look too much alike?
What? Conversely?
Was it that close? Maybe.
Please talk to all three of us.
I'm in.
I'm the senior.
I am.
You're a senior.
What have you two been up to lately?
I'm taking lessons at home for the FC event.
I'm doing the same.
What?
You're definitely not doing that, are you?
Yes, I am.
Huh? Don't play games with me!
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know.
Come on, senior sound!
Come on, make your noise!
Gaga!
Gaga?
It's a little flickering.
That's funny.
It's terrible. It doesn't look like him. It's like grass.
Don't say grass.
Well, that's all for now.
Now then, I would like to ask for comments on your goals for the year 2022.
Please tell us.
Please let us know.
Mirei, your voice is dry.
Too much of the usual Aya-chan.
It's the usual Aya-chan.
I'll go to many Ebichun concerts.
And spring tour, too.
I'll be there.
That's right.
By all means.
I'll do my best!
Quite a lot of yunos.
Stay healthy.
Great.
I'm moving out.
Lose 20 pounds.
Oh, great.
That's great.
That's the first time I've ever lost weight.
Heh.
I recommend running.
I'm gonna cut my stuff in half.
Oh, it's all the stuff.
He wants to increase his knowledge.
Oh, I know what you mean.
He wants to be smarter.
Giant Representative?
Yeah, giant delegate.
He wants to win the lottery.
I wanna win!
Have you ever won the lottery?
Aren't we not allowed to say that? I'm not supposed to say anything about that.
Yes, I have.
I didn't score high.
It's not good if it's a single ticket.
It's OK if it's only 500 yen or so.
Scratch tickets, you know,
We all bought tickets once before, didn't we?
We did! And for the live concert,
At the live concert, at the lottery ticket booth in front of the International Borland amusement park,The concert was at the lottery ticket booth in front of the International Borland amusement park station,
We gathered around in front of the lottery ticket booth.
We had a little extra time, since everyone was still coming,
Do you want to play a little?
We scratched.
It's the day of the concert.
Did you win? That's when.
Did you win?
Was it 200 yen or 300 yen?
It was 300 yen.
Did you win?
It said something about a Valentine's Day ride.
Valentine's Day?
It's coming soon, isn't it?
It's almost next month, or almost next month.
Do you think she'll confess her feelings?
He wants to give her a valentine.
I hope so.
I'm going to get into the university of my first choice.
That's right. It's exam season.
That's right.
Hmm.
He's getting 100 chocolates.
Good luck.
Take some cardboard boxes home with you.
I don't know if I can get it, but take the cardboard anyway.
Yeah, I'll just wait like this with a cardboard box.
Now I'm waiting.
It's important to have a regular life.
It's important.
It's important, but... it's hard, isn't it?
It's hard.
I'm going on a fashion diet.
Oh, that's good.
I'm going to try a new cuisine.
There are a lot of new dishes.
I want to go on vacation. I want to go on vacation.
And Corona. I can't wait for it to stop.
I know, right?
We'll be able to go to the restaurant.
That's a great idea. A temple hobby.
I passed the Chinese proficiency test!
I didn't know Chinese was an English language system.
I wonder how it's put together.
Is it a backward reading system?
But I wonder if it's written in Chinese characters, our Chinese characters.
I guess there are some non-Japanese kanji that are similar to ours.
Maybe it's easier to learn.
Mire-chan studied Chinese in college.
That's how I did it.
If she could speak Chinese, she'd be strong.
I tell her it's Chinese, so it's close to English.
Oh, it's close to English.
It's similar to English here.
He says he's been to the sauna over 100 times.
Oh, that's nice.
I also go to sauna.
That's a lot.
We just started, so we have about 11 months to go,
Let's all make what we can achieve come true.
Let's make it happen.
Yes, that's right.
This is the 41st edition of EBICHU's delightful and fun showroom.
The ending came in a flash.
The first half of the showroom is already talking about a super beautiful woman.
Osawa-kun, what will be the memory of seeing everyone's showroom today?
Seasoning.
Is it the seasoning?
Sasuseso.
Sassusesuso is good.
I'll get you some Sashisusiso for now.
I'll get it.
Let's cook.
Let's do our best.
Okay, I guess.
Is it okay if I interfere?
I hope you can all help.
No, not this. I'll do my best.
Not this.
I'm going to do my best here.
And then, and then, and then.
How am I going to do it? It's too hard.
How do you do it? Tell me.
Tell me.
The first word is "A".
Well, first of all, yes, this way.
FC members only event,
FHF members-only Fan Appreciation Day 2022 will be held
Saturday, February 12th,
The event will be held on Saturday, February 12, at the Pacifico Yokohama National Grand Hall in Kanagawa Prefecture.
The event will be held in two parts, with the first part starting at 12:00 pm and the second part starting at 5:00 pm,
The third round of ticket acceptance is now open,
The third round of ticket acceptance ends today at 23:59.
If you join the fan club now, you can still make it in time,
I hope you will all come and enjoy the show.
I wonder what we will do this year.
I wonder if we will have a little party.
Party?
I think we're going to have a party.
What do you think, Nino?
What are your hopes for the FC event?What are your hopes for the FC event?
This is my first fan club,
I am looking forward to meeting you all.
What is it?
I want to be good to everyone, not hard,
Something, not good, something,
It's real.
It's very, very real.
I'll do my best!
The two new members are going to do their best too!
Mie-chan will do her best too.
Mie-chan will eat delicious food.
And on a personal note,
Kashiya Kimoto center solar get is 2022,
Interviews are in February and March.
The general sale will start at 10:00 on Saturday the 29th,
Please come and join us for 12 performances at 6 venues.
We are looking forward to seeing you there.
Yay!
And I don't have the details yet,
We will be holding the Ebichu Spring Tour starting in March.
We will be going to a lot of shows this time as well, 16 places I think.
Please come and visit us.
And on March 23rd,
Shiritsu Ebichu 7th full album,
Shiritsu Ebi Chugaku" will be released on March 23rd.
I am so excited!
The album will be released in two months.
I still only have Enieni,
But recording, recording, recording,
But the recording is going well,
It's going great,
I don't know where to go with this,
I don't know how much I can say, but I hope that you, the fans, will be able to feel the process of making this album,
I hope that you, the fans, can feel the process of making the album and enjoy it with us,
We've been doing a lot of projects on Twitter and so on,
I have a feeling that the album will be an album that everyone can enjoy together,
I have a feeling that the album will be an album that everyone can enjoy together, and we are still not sure what songs will be included,
We are still unsure of what songs will be on the album and what songs will be on it,
We are looking forward to making it together with everyone,
We are looking forward to making this album together with everyone,
I hope you are all looking forward to the spring tour and the excitement we are all going to have together,
I look forward to seeing you all on the spring tour.
Now, let's announce the final ranking.
Here we go.
Fifth place, Jam.
Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Ms. Hana.
Third place,
First place, Yoshishino Kashiwagi.
Second place, Ms. Yukitsu.
First place, Mr. Po-chan Film.
Yes, ah, happy stage.
What's up?
Bye bye.
We've been waiting for No. 0, haven't we?
No. 0 is...
Zero first place goes to Energy Ace.
And so, this is the 41st edition of the MBC's Delightful and Funny Showroom.
Today is the end of this hour,
I have an important announcement.
Today's broadcast is,
Watch it.
I'm still watching it.
Surprise!
I wonder what kind of members and when the next trio will come,
I hope everyone is looking forward to it.
After the delivery, there will be a meeting to reflect on the event,
The parents are also going to confess their feelings,
I wonder what today's review meeting will be like.
What should we do, really?
What if they get really angry?
Don't worry,
If they can see us as monocaust,
We are not angry with ourselves.
Oh, that's right.
That's not fair.
So, let's have a reflection meeting then,
Let's join in the reflection meeting.
If you have anything you want to say at the meeting, please make a note of it,
If you have anything you want to say at the meeting, please write it down and send it to me in the comments,
I'll be waiting.
I'll be waiting for you,
Let's have fun together for a little while afterwards.
I'll be waiting for you. That's all for today,
That's all for today.
Thank you very much.
This is Chibi Bestie Book.
Riko Nakayama and her friends.
Oh, that's right.
Please check it out.
See you soon.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work.
I guess it was a little awful.
Today.
What is it?
I knew it. You've been here for a long time.
You've been cooking for a long time, but you can't tell me what you're cooking?I'm not sure I can tell you the layers of culinary restraints.
And I want at least one of them to know.
If all three of us don't know what's going on...
It's a little bit difficult.
But from Millet's point of view, I don't think she needed to know.
I don't think she needed to know about it, but I don't think the two of them studied enough.
I'm going to study harder from now on.
Gekino.
Yes, I'll study.
Yes, I said.
Well, well, I think it would be good if you could make use of that next time.
Yes, I'm sure I'll do it.
Please do. Well, please close.
Yes, thank you all. Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much.